

## **Profile**

Experienced and proficient in languages that help with web development and data engineering. Gained experience and exposure from university projects, beta testing software for a digital audio workstation called "Audio Design Desk", gained certificates from courses provided, and worked on projects revolving around web development and data analytics.

# **Employment History**

## Data Engineer, Capgemini, Remote

MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

- Gain training from certificates
- Learn how to clean data, analyze data, and present it through visualizations
- Learn how to use Python libraries, such as Pandas, Tensorflow, Numpy, etc.
- Placed on projects revolving around web development and data analytics
- Satisfy the client's needs for a specific project by planning and executing effectively
- Able to use some front-end knowledge of HTML, CSS, and Javascript
- Learn to use cloud services like AWS or Azure

## Beta Test Intern, Audio Design Desk, Los Angeles, CA

JANUARY 2022 - MARCH 2022

- Follow build test routines to find errors or bugs, and report them accordingly
- Test metadata software that helps organize and categorize audio files
- Close, open, or update issues within GitHub for the software
- Report any issues or bugs to QC Lead
- Copy and paste the console log output of any bug

## Education

# Computer Science, California Polytechnic State University, Pomona, Pomona, CA

AUGUST 2018 - DECEMBER 2020

Graduated with a Bachelor's of Computer Science with a 3.69 GPA (Magna Cum Laude)

Joined the Game Dev Club from September 2019 - December 2019

#### Mathematics (AS-T), Citrus College, Glendora, CA

JUNE 2015 - JUNE 2018

# **Projects**

## **Trend Anomaly Detector Web App**

- A web app using Python and Streamlit
- It detects trend anomalies in specifically formatted excel files

## **COVID-19 Test Appointment Scheduler Website Server**

- A website server coded in C and database uses SQLite
- A server that hosts a website that schedules appointments for COVID-19 tests

## **Details**

Glendora

United States

6268276044

musicmaker773@gmail.com

## Links

LinkedIn

**GitHub** 

Portfolio

## Skills

Microsoft Excel

PHP

Microsoft Office

MySQL

C++

HTML & CSS

SQL

Git

JavaScript

Java

Python

Google Drive

Microsoft Power BI

AWS

Streamlit

# References

Zal Colah from Audio Design Desk

zal@add.app

**Delfino Neira from Los Angeles County** 

8054551926

Dave Johannsen from California State Polytechnic University, Pomona

dljohannsen@cpp.edu | 9098694195

Maurice Bello from Uber

6268907185

**Devendra Patel from Fresno County** 

dpatel@fresnocountyca.gov | 5594178360